George Brooks Additional Papers /4148
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
George Brooks Additional Papers
1969-1994
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Brooks, George W.
/4148
28 cubic feet
28 linear ft.
Papers (documents).
8016899
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, June 18, 2014
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, October 03, 2016
Biographical / Historical
George Brooks (July 12, 1908 January 27, 2000) was a professor at Cornell University's School of Industrial and Labor Relations.
A graduate of Yale University (BA, 1930) and Brown University (MA, 1932), Brooks worked for the National Mediation Board, National Labor Relations Board, and the International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulfite, and Paper Mill Workers until he joined the ILR School in 1961. Brooks published in the Industrial and Labor Relations Review, Cornell Law Review, Review of Law and Social Change, and Monthly Labor Review.
See the Cornell University Faculty Memorial Statement for Professor George Brooks: http://ecommons.library.cornell.edu/handle/1813/17900
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /4003: ILR School ILR Service Training Course Manuals /4098: George Brooks Additional Papers /4112: George Brooks Additional Papers 5860: U.S. Department of Labor "Labor Organization Annual Report Forms, LM- 2"
Brooks, George; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations
8016899
- ILR School and Extension, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Human Affairs Program 2/73, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Extension - General, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Reporting to 10-72, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Extension labor education, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- "Union Leader as a Decision Maker", 1963 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Report, Sessions, Case Studios, 1962-1963 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Teacher Training 1990 National Elevator Industries, Inc., 1979-1990 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Administrative & Training, 1978-1980 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Training Material, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- 1983 Program Bal Harbour (Box 1, Folder 11)
- NEII June '85 Board of Directors meeting, California, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Joint conferences, Dairyman - Teamsters, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Teamster Conferences, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Dairymen's Conferences, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Chicago Pneumatic Tool Co. 11/18/78, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Hardinge Bros., 1983-1988 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Administrative 1979-1982 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Hardinge - Training Material, Notes, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Training Material & Work Material, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Sessions, outlines 79-1981 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Meetings with Management, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Consumers Power, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Schedules, arrangements, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Development of Program, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Teachers, 1981-1983 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Work Material, 1979-1983 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Training Material 1979-1982 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Catalogs and related mat'l, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Sessions, Lists of Participants, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Agreements, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Evaluations 1982, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Meetings with Management, Follow-up, Reports; Article, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Crouse-Hinds, GTE, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Administrative, Preparation, 1987-1989 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Training Material - Danvers, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Preparation Salem, 1985-1988 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- "Line-by-Line" Training, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Pensions, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Paper Union - Pension plans, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Pension Tabulations, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Union, 1976-1989 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- National Officers - elections, 1965-1992 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Union Executive boards, article, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- EX Bd DRAFTS, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- White Collar workers, 1962-1988 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Union Finances & Disciplinary Action, 1985-1988 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Revenue, expenditures, 1972-1986 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Construction & Transportation, 1981-1986 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Trade and Service, 1976-1986 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Retail Clerks, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Entertainment, 1971-1987 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- MFG - Primary Metal, 1973-1986 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Boilermakers, 1981-1986 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- MFG - Trans. Equipment, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- MFG - Communications, printing, publishing, 1970-1977 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- MFG, 1966-1989 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Paper Industry Final Reports, 1948-1971 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Government, education, 1965-1989 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Financial Reports AFT, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Finances Baker, 1976-1979 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Finances, 1968-1986 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Collective bargaining; const prov., 1973-1985 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- CB DOL 1978-1980 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Economic effects & gov't regulation, 1959-1971 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Unions and anti-trust law, 1947-1973 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- AFL-CIO, 1954-1992 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- U nion General Files, 1961-1992 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Assoc. for Union Democracy, 1982-1992 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- $50+ Club News, 1989-1993 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- AUD Publications and UDA, 1955-1994 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Union Democracy Review (Box 4, Folder 15)
- New Politics, Legal framework of Bargaining, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Collective Bargaining & union-management relations, 1969-1992 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Ritual, Collusion, 1966-1974 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- NLRB cases, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- General Electric, 1964-1971 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- GE 1969-1979 negotiations & strike (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Boulwarism, 1964-1976 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Auto, 1969-1973 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Variety, 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Union Mergers, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Paper Industry, 1976-1981 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Printing Industry, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Merger study Railroads - UTU, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- United Transportation Union, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Steelworkers, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Merger Study Steelworkers, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Finances UTU and Merger, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- LM-2 Forms and instructions, 1959-1979 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Lists of Unions, Outline lists, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Introductions, Sources, 1980-1987 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Union Corruption, 1979-1986 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- President's Comm. On Org'd Crime, 1975-1986 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Report; outlines, drafts, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Work Material Notes, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Report Editor's Notes, 1985-1986 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- New York Construction, 1986-1988 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Organized Crime, Teamster Trusteeship, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Cornell Law School 8-4-79, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Dade County, Miami 1-23-78, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Organized Crime ILR 1988 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Construction Painters, 1966-1972 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Transportation Teamsters, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Alternatives to Strikes, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- International Paper Company - Employee's Retirement Plan, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- History, 1952-1964 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Conventions (Oinc. Corresp.), 1959 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Executive Board, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Meeting, 1963 - minutes (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Finances, 1951-1962 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Organizing Bargaining, 1949-1958 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Research and Education, 1949-1962 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Hamilton Paper #769, 1959-1960 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- South, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- United Paper Workers Int'l Union, 1973-1992 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Handbook, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Mailing Lists, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Information activities, Mid Atlantic & New England, 1961-1962 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Midwest + Southeast, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Canada, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Issues, 1953-1962 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Collective Bargaining, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Campaign, General, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Corruption, 1957-1978 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Pension Plan, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- The Rebel, 1990-1993 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- AWPPW & The Leaflet, 1987-1992 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Suits re local funds, 1955-1965 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Court Records & Other, 1967-1968 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Paper Workers, 1964-1989 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- UPP revolt, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Rank File for Membership Rights, 1961-1963 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- 1960 Revolt (Box 8, Folder 14)
- AFL-CIO, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Collective Bargaining, 1963-1964 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- World Trade IAM Conference & Post Office Training, 1963-1964 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- New York City Classes, Postal Clerks, Letter Carriers, Review, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- List of Unions, 1988-1989 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Guidebook Tables, 1987-1989 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Construction, 1963-1976 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Construction ms, 1986-1988 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Carpenters, 1941-1987 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Laborers, 1981-1984 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Plumbing, 1980-1981 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Operating Engineers, 1984-1989 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Sheet Metal, 1974-1978 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Iron Workers, 1976-1986 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Painters, 1942-1960 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Bricklayers, 1981-1984 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Plasterers, 1975-1984 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Elevator Constructors, 1986-1990 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Teamster papers., 1961-1990 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Teamsters - Lippman special paper, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Teamsters misc., 1953-1973 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Rail and Air transportation, 1939-1984 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Amalgamated Transit Union, 1981-1988 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Transport Workers, 1971-1981 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Transportation Communications Union, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Railway Clerks, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Railway Carmen, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- UTU, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- UTU Student Papers, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Officers, Structure, 1966-1975 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Maintenance of Way, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Locomotive Engineers, 1972-1987 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Airline Pilots 1, 1977-1982 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Masters, Mates and Pilots; Radio Assn. & Others, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- PATCO, 1968-1977 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Firemen & Oilers, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- ILA, 1987-1989 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- ILWU, 1982-1991 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Seafarers, 1942-1983 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- MEBA (and NMU), 1988 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- NMU, 1983-1987 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Trade and Service, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- UFCW, 1954-1986 (Box 10, Folder 22)
- RWDS, 1966-1978 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Service Employees, 1981-1992 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Hotel, 1981-1986 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Office & Professional, 1960-1983 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Healthcare - 80's & Constitution, 1967-1983 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- New York City Hospital, 1969-1984 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Local 1199, 1989-1992 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Dept. of Health NY Medicaid Law conf. Dec' 84, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- American Nurses Association, 1976-1984 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Musicians & Entertainment, 1968-1989 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Screen actors Guild & Actors Equity, 1967-1986 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- AFTRA, 1984-1989 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- IATSE, 1976-1984 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- AAAA. Screen Actors, Actors Equity, 1963-1983 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- United Mine Workers Papers by Hanauer and Deliket, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Papers, other students with constitutions, 1963-1983 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Steelworkers, 1953-1974 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Boilermakers, 1981-1990 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Utility, 1977-1982 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Aluminum, Brick and Glass Workers, 1985-1989 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Glass & Ceramic, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Transportation Equipment, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Transportation Equipment, 1981-1987 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- UAW, Auto Workers outlines, student papers, etc., 1986-1987 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- UAW Public Review, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- UAW Collective Barg., 1968-1973 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- UAW - New Directions, 1989-1993 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Manufacturing Primary Metal, 1984-1986 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- IBEW, 1946-1982 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- IAM Machinists, 1961-1985 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- IUE constitutions, 1985-1987 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Allied Industrial Workers, 1981-1983 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Pattern Makers, 1976-1982 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Shipbuilding, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Typographical Union, 1961-1976 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Printing Industry, 1963-1969 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Graphic Communications, 1974-1993 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- GAIU, 1968-1974 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Media Employees International Union (MEIU), 1983 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Newspaper Guild, 1950-1981 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Telecommunications, 1974-1987 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers, 1976-1990 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Ladies Garment Workers, 1937-1983 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- United Textile Workers of America, 1901 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Wood, Paper, Petro-chemical (Box 13, Folder 9)
- International Woodworkers of America, 1957-1962 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- United Paperworkers, 1984-1991 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Paperworkers, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- C/B Seminar AWPPW 1968 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Bakery, Confectionary, and Tobacco Workers, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Misc. Mfg - Food Grain Millers Distillery Workers, 1983-1990 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Oil, Petrochemical, and Related Groups, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers (OCAW), 1938-1985 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers, 1978-1981 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Glass Molders Pottery Plastics & Allied, 1981-1989 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Flint Glass Workers, 1981-1989 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- Chemical Workers, 1946-1981 (Box 13, Folder 21)
- Checkoff, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- New York State, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- PERB News, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Joint Leg Cttee, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Annual Report 1964 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Final Report December 1964 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Schools New York State, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Schools New York City, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Org'n of Public Employees, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Non-Profit NYC Hospitals, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Conf. on L-M Relins in Public Serv. (Misc & Unclassified), 1964 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Report Distribution, 1964-1965 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Minimum Wage, cb, regulating unions, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Unions in Federal Government, 1943-1978 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- AFGE (Govt Emp), 1962-1982 (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Treasury Employees, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Post Office, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- Letter Carriers, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 18)
- Letter Carriers NALC Constitutions, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 19)
- Rural Letter Carriers, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 20)
- AFSCME Papers, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- AFSCME - constitution, 1946 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- AFSCME Council 50, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- CSEA - constitutions, agreements, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Fire Fighters, 1945 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Teachers AFT, 1986-1989 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- NEA, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- AAUP, 1976-1980 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Discrimination, 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- 1964 Report, 1964-1965 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Commission of Human Rights, 1964-1966 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Discrimination by Union, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Apprenticeship, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Sheet Metal Workers Case (Local 28), 1964 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- County government, Pennsylvania, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 15)
- State Law, 1971-1980 (Box 15, Folder 16)
- Tioga County, 1971-1974 (Box 15, Folder 17)
- Representation, 1974-1981 (Box 15, Folder 18)
- Bradford County, 1970-1985 (Box 15, Folder 19)
- Mike McGovern, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 20)
- Administrative, 1979-1981 (Box 15, Folder 21)
- Commissioners Actions, Agenda, 1976-1984 (Box 15, Folder 22)
- Campaign - Manor 1980 (Box 15, Folder 23)
- Representation (1974) (Box 15, Folder 24)
- Election at Manor 3/6/75, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 25)
- Campaign - Manor 1980 (Box 15, Folder 26)
- Schedules through 1/1/80, 1979-1980 (Box 15, Folder 27)
- Mental Health - Mental Retardation, 1978-1980 (Box 15, Folder 28)
- MH-HR Agreement, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 29)
- New York City, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 30)
- Bargaining, General, 1963-1975 (Box 15, Folder 31)
- Units, Jean Savage ms, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 32)
- Transit, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 33)
- Welfare, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 34)
- Rival Unionism SSEU, 1967-1972 (Box 15, Folder 35)
- George W. Brooks, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Courses, Lecture etc., 1969-1981 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Historical perspectives on American Labor, 1963-1985 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Labor History, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Early history (guilds), 1939 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Chronologies (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Courses by Others, 1948 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Documentary Center, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Courses, 1979-1990 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Guest Lecturers General, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- ILR 683 sp 82, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- ILR 683 Politics & Govt of Unions, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Union Administration, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- ILR 451 (1961) related to ILR 605 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- (1964) ILR 605 Administration, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- (1967) ILR 605 Administrative (Box 16, Folder 16)
- Employee Organ. In Government, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 17)
- (1965) Sessions (Box 16, Folder 18)
- (1965) Axelrod (Box 16, Folder 19)
- (1965) Cordova (1965) Goodman (Box 16, Folder 20)
- Morgenstein (1965) Kaplan (1965) (Box 16, Folder 21)
- (1965) Rosensweig (1965) J. Pezet (Box 16, Folder 22)
- (1965) R. Smith (1965) Schnapp (Box 16, Folder 23)
- Bozotto, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 24)
- Bronson, John, 1987-1990 (Box 16, Folder 25)
- Doyle, Larry, 1988-1992 (Box 16, Folder 26)
- Kennedy, George, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 27)
- Leahy, Jack, 1990-1992 (Box 16, Folder 28)
- Raynor, Bruce, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 29)
- Rochester, Michael, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 30)
- Ryan, David, 1978-1988 (Box 16, Folder 31)
- Ryan, Stephen, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 32)
- Scarselletta, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 33)
- Tanner, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 34)
- ILR 301 F '91 Evaluation, 1958-1991 (Box 16, Folder 35)
- ILR 508 (1964) Student Papers (Box 16, Folder 36)
- ILR 301 'F 92 Attendance, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- ILR 301 'F 92 Administrative, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- ILR 301 'F 92 Reserve List, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- ILR 301 'F 92 Grades, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- ILR 301 'F 92 Evaluation, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- ILR 301 'F 92 Sessions, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- ILR 301 'F 92 Syllabus, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- ILR 301 'F 92 Term Paper, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- ILR 301 'F 92 Discussions, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- ILR 301 'F 92 Material Distributed, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- ILR 301 'F 92 Exams, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Spring 1992 (Box 17, Folder 12)
- ILR 301 'S 92 Administrative, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 13)
- ILR 301 'S 92 Reserve List, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 14)
- ILR 301 'S 92 Grades, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 15)
- ILR 301 'S 92 Evaluation, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 16)
- ILR 301 'S 92 Sessions, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 17)
- ILR 301 'S 92 Syllabus, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 18)
- ILT 301 'S 92 Term Paper, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 19)
- ILR 301 S '92 Exams, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 20)
- Fall 1991 (Box 17, Folder 21)
- ILR 301 F' 91 Current, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 22)
- ILR 301 F'91 Attendance, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 23)
- ILR 301 F' 91 Administrative, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 24)
- ILR 301 F' 91 Grades, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 25)
- ILR 301 F '91 Sessions, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 26)
- ILR 301 F '91 Syllabus, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 27)
- ILR 301 F' 91 Term Papers, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 28)
- ILR 301 F' 91 Discussion Groups, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 29)
- ILR 301 F' 91 Material distributed, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 30)
- ILR 301 F' 91 Examinations, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 31)
- ILR 301 Spring 1991 (Box 17, Folder 32)
- Spring '91 Attendance, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 33)
- Shenkan paper, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 34)
- ILR 301 sp 91 Administrative, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 35)
- ILR 301 S 91 Reserve List, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 36)
- ILR 301 S 91 Grades, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 37)
- ILR 301 S 91 Grades, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 38)
- ILR 301 S 91 Evaluation, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 39)
- ILR 301 Sp 91 Sessions, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 40)
- ILR 301 So 91 Syllabus, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 41)
- ILR 301 S '91 Term Papers, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 42)
- ILR 301 S '91 Evaluation, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 43)
- ILR 301 S '91 Discussion groups, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 44)
- ILR 301 S '91 Discussion groups, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 45)
- ILR 301 S '91 Material distributed, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 46)
- ILR 301 S '91 Examinations, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 47)
- ILR 301 Fall 1990 (Box 17, Folder 48)
- ILR 301 F '90 Administrative, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 49)
- ILR 301 F '90 Grades, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 50)
- ILR 301 F '90 Evaluations, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 51)
- ILR 301 F '90 Sessions, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 52)
- ILR 301 F' 90 Term Papers, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 53)
- ILR 301 S '92 Material Distributed, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 54)
- ILR 301 F '90 Material Distributed, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 55)
- ILR 301 F '90 Examinations, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 56)
- ILR 301 Spring 1990 (Box 17, Folder 57)
- ILR 301 Sp 90 Administrative, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 58)
- ILR 301 Sp 90 Grades, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 59)
- ILR 301 Sp 90 Evaluations, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 60)
- ILR 301 Sp 90 Term Papers, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 61)
- ILR 301 Sp 90 Material Distributed, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 62)
- Preliminary examinations, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 63)
- ILR 301 Summary outline, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 64)
- Teamsters (Current), 1990 (Box 17, Folder 65)
- Spring 1993 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Fall 1992 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- ILR 301 Fall 1989 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- ILR 301 Spring 1989 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- ILR 301 Fall 1988 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- ILR 301 Spring 1988 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- ILR 301 Fall 1987 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- ILR 301 Spring 1987 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- ILR 301 F '86, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 9)
- ILR 301 S '86, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 10)
- ILR 301 F '85, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 11)
- ILR 301 Sp '85, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 12)
- ILR 301 Fall 84, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 13)
- ILR 301 Sp 84, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 14)
- ILR 301 Fall 82, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 15)
- ILR 301 F 80, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 16)
- ILR 301 F 79, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 17)
- ILR 301 S 79 Administration, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 18)
- ILR 301 Fall 1977 (Box 18, Folder 19)
- ILR 301 Spring 1976 (Box 18, Folder 20)
- ILR 301 Fall 1975 (Box 18, Folder 21)
- ILR 301 Fall 1974 (Box 18, Folder 22)
- ILR 301 Spring 1974 (Box 18, Folder 23)
- ILR 301 Fall 1973 (Box 18, Folder 24)
- ILR 301 Fall 1972 (Box 18, Folder 25)
- ILR 301 Spring 1972 (Box 18, Folder 26)
- ILR 301 Fall 1971 (Box 18, Folder 27)
- ILR 301 Spring 1971 (Box 18, Folder 28)
- ILR 301 Fall 1970 (Box 18, Folder 29)
- ILR 301 Fall 1969 (Box 18, Folder 30)
- ILR 301 Fall 1968 (Box 18, Folder 31)
- ILR 301 Fall 1967 (Box 18, Folder 32)
- ILR 301 Fall 1966 (Box 18, Folder 33)
- ILR 402 Field courses, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 34)
- 1969 Transit Authority (Box 18, Folder 35)
- 1970 Local 1199 (Box 18, Folder 36)
- (1969) ILR 402 Reading Lists (Box 18, Folder 37)
- 1965 ILR 505 Labor History (Box 18, Folder 38)
- 1962-1964 ILR 505 Labor History (Box 18, Folder 39)
- ILR 100 Spring 1972 (Box 18, Folder 40)
- ILR 100 Spring 1971 (Box 18, Folder 41)
- ILR 100 Spring 1970 (Box 18, Folder 42)
- ILR 100 Spring 1969 (Box 18, Folder 43)
- ILR 200 Fall 1968 (Box 18, Folder 44)
- 1965 ILR 505 Term Papers (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Lectures notes, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Lectures notes Outlines, 1968-1972 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Dev. Of Ind'l Rel'ns Training Program ILR 508, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- ILR 508 development of Ind'l Relns Training Programs, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 5)